

Robert Sabados

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

robert.sabados.se@gmail.com

Zaharija Orfelina 25, Subotica 24000, Serbia

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- React / Angular / Vue
- Node / Express
- Laravel / Symfony / Yii2
- Django / Flask

EDUCATION INFO:

University of Szeged Bachelor in Computer Science 2006-2010

- Programming skills and software engineering.
- Web development
- Information processing.

ABOUT ME

I am a senior front end developer who has 7+ years of experience in web and mobile UI / UX development using Best JS frameworks including Vue, React and Angular.

As a passionate developer and fast learner, I am always ready to dedicate to the client's idea and planning at the top of technologies.

It's important to me to build long term relationships with clients, so I am mainly looking for long term projects and keeping high qualities on my work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nutanix (Apr. 2019 - Nov. 2020)

Senior Full Stack Developer

- Develop express.js application using node.js
- Design DB with MongoDB, building middleware
- Administration Linux servers
- Building several RESTFul API
- Integration with FB/VK/Instagram api
- Implemented vanilla JS Frontend

Auction (May. 2017 - Mar. 2019)

Senior Full Stack Developer

- Assisted in developing a user-friendly website that increased revenue by 97%.
- Updated the UI based on the new design and increased visitor clicks by 199.8%.
- Revamped our security applications and diminished hacker attacks from 4.19% to 0.09%.
- Created the reusable React components.
- Built pixel-perfect and mobile-responsive pages using AntD.
- Managed global state using Redux and implemented various form validations(synchronous and asynchronous mode) using the Redux Form.
- Used Redux-Saga as a middleware and Reselect as a selector
- Developed the Back-End RESTful APIs using Node.js.
- Made some enhancements of MongoDB architecture to improve performance and scalability.
- Deployed the app to the Amazon EC2 instance.
- Added a hot module replacement plugin to Webpack.
- Built an admin dashboard to manage the contents.

TradeCore (Apr. 2014 - Apr. 2017)

Frontend Developer

- Building Social project to management booking.
- Developed, from scratch, a SPA's front-end using React.
- Built reusable React components for data visualization.
- Created reusable JavaScript modules for data manipulation.
- Constructed a framework using React, Redux, and Ant design.
- Developed Node and Laravel back-end APIs using Redis and PostgreSQL.

RT-RK (May. 2012 - Jan. 2014)

Software Programmer

- Built a secure medical DNA sharing platform using Ethereum smart contract.
- Developed projects using Laravel.
- Developed backend using PostgreSQL.
- Google Cloud Platform deployment using docker.
- Analytics platform for Amazon merchants, similar to Sellics.
- Using AWS Lambda, AWS Aurora DB to develop backend APIs.